http://www.fibre2fashion.com/aboutus/policy.asp

We use cookies for better user experience. By continuing to browse this site you agree to its Cookie Policy or can decide to change your browser settings anytime. Got it
×
Sponsored
ECO PULSARS - A more sustainable way to wind the yarn | Discover More
BUSINESS
KNOWLEDGE
Market Intelligence
News
Articles
TRADE FAIRS & EVENTS
MEMBERSHIP PLANS
F2FMART
Corporate Membership
One-stop solution for branding, networking, research & recruitment.
Premium Membership
Widen your business network
Market Research Solutions
Price Trends, Insight, Customized Research information for all research needs.
Strategic Consulting Services
Derive maximum value from acquisitions through proven practices
Fashion Accelerator
Launch - Build - Grow
Taking fashion & lifestyle brands online
Recruitment Solutions
Hire the apt talent for your organization
Trade Fair & Event promotion
Promote your Trade Fair, Event or Expo with our holistic Event Marketing Solutions
Brand Building Solutions
Create a positive brand image
Advertise
Get your copy
F2FMART
JOIN FREE
SIGN IN
InquiryNow
Please fill in your details to download the Table of Contents of this report for free. We also do customization of these reports so you can write to us at mi@fibre2fashion.com
in case you need any other additional information.
Name
Company
Email
Phone Number
Country
Select Country
Afghanistan
Albania
Policy
This Privacy Policy was last updated on 24th May 2018.
At F2F.com we understand
the care you assign towards usage and sharing of your information and we
appreciate your unwavering trust that we will do so carefully. This notice
describes our privacy
policy.
The  Fibre2Fashion
Private Limited  (hereinafter collectively referred to as
"fibre2fashion.com",
"F2F", "We", "Us" or "Our") Privacy Policy describes how we collect,
use, and
disclose information when you visit or use our website
www.fibre2fashion.com
("Site") , subscribe to our magazine in the
name of ‘Fibre2Fashion’ ,
our mobile and website applications including but not
limited to MyF2F, News App, Market
Intelligence App, Magazine App, Jobs App,
eCAAS App, Texpro (the "Apps"), any other website or
mobile application that
links to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the "Services").
By visiting F2F or using our Services you are accepting the practices
described in this
Privacy Notice.
Some key terms
In our Privacy Policy, when we refer to:
"Customers" (hereinafter
collectively referred to as "You", "Your", "User"), we mean our customers who use
our Services, including visitors to our sites.
"Your Content", we mean any information provided by you as a result of
usage of our services
This policy covers the below mentioned:
What personal information about Customers does F2F
Use of Information
How we use Cookies and Similar Technologies?
Sharing of Information
Storage and Transfer of Personal Information
Security of your information
Advertising and links to other sites
What rights you have?
Privacy of Children
California Do Not Track
Questions/Changes to policy
What personal information about Customers does F2F collect?
The information we learn from customers can be
broadly classified into four categories as mentioned below, such information
helps us personalize and continually improve our services and hence your
experience:
Information You Provide Us:
We
receive and store any information you enter on our site or give us in any other
way. For example, during sign up you provide us with name, , business
information, including but not limited to address, email, designation, phone
number and URL.   You can choose not to provide certain
information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our
features. We use the information that you provide for purposes such
as responding to your requests, to connect with prospective buyers and sellers,
and communicating with you.
Information
we collect automatically:
We
receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us.
For example, like many sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain
types of information when your Web browser accesses fibre2fashion.com or advertisements
served by or on behalf of fibre2fashion.com on other sites.
Via
Mobile or Smartphones:
When
you download or use our apps, we may receive certain information. For example, information about your location or the unique identifier for
your device
.
We may use this information to provide you with location-based services, such
as advertising and personalization. You may restrict the permissions you provide
to our apps, however by doing so you may not be able to access the full features
of our apps.
Information
from Other Sources:
F2F Apps and Site may
include buttons, tools, or information that link to other third-party services
(for example, a Facebook "Comment" button). We may collect
information about your use of these features. In addition, when you see or
interact with these buttons, tools, or information, or view a F2F web page or
App containing them, some information from your browser may automatically
be sent to the other company.
Please
read that company’s privacy policy for more information.
You can refer to the list of third parties here.
Use of Information
We may use your personal information
including but not limited to the following purposes:
To administer your use of our Services
To facilitate buyer and supplier connect.
To better understand your needs and interests
To better understand and improvise our products and services
To facilitate your use and personalizing your
experience on the Site
To serve you relevant ads
To book your ads that we will display on website
and apps
To respond to your inquiries or fulfilling your
requests for information about our Services
To provide you with information about our
Services and sending you information and materials from F2F including marketing
communication
To help you address problems with the Site,
including any technical problems
To Process online job application, you have
applied for
To detect and prevent identity theft, fraud, and
other potentially illegal acts as well as protecting the integrity of the
website
To respond to subpoenas, court orders, or
judicial processes
To provide information to law enforcement
agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public
safety
To resolve disputes and troubleshoot problems
To help with any investigations or complaints
To provide you with relevant information or
Services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you based on
previous interactions, where you have consented to be contacted
We use the information we collect in
a variety of ways. Generally, using all of the above mentioned, and similar
type tools, we may collect, aggregate, and use information from or about
you such as data about the type of browser and operating system used,
which web pages you view, the time and duration or you visits to our Site, the
search queries you may use on the Site, whether you clicked on any
advertisements, whether you have clicked on any links in any e-mails sent from
us, or third-parties on our behalf and whether you have chosen to opt-out of
certain services or information sharing.
How we use Cookies and Similar Technologies?
Cookies are bits of electronic
information that a website may transfer to a visitor's computer to identify
specific information about the visitor's visits to a website. The Site uses a
browser feature known as a cookie, which assigns a unique identification to
your computer, in case you do not wish us to collect such information kindly
refer to our cookie policy to opt out. You can access the details of our Cookie
Policy here.
If you want to delete any cookies
that are already on your computer, please refer to the instructions for your
file management software to locate the file or directory that store cookies.
Alternatively, you may wish to visit http://www.aboutcookies.org which contains comprehensive
information on how to manage cookies on a wide variety of browsers. However,
please note that if you disable the use of cookies on your computer, some
functionalities of our Services will not work.
Sharing of Information
F2F provides your personal information to
third parties who are obligated
to use the personal information that F2F shares with them for the
purpose of provision of their services to us in order to help us run our
business. These third parties include but are not limited to business partners,
suppliers, sub-contractors, advertisers & advertising networks, analytics
& search engine providers, payment providers. We may also share with third parties
aggregate information or information that does not personally identify you.
Should you require more details on third parties
we work with or have any questions around it, please click here to know more about the third parties we work
with.
For example, we use several payment
gateways (one among which is HDFC bank) to manage our payments, but we reserve
the right to change this service provider at any time for any reason.. Your
credit card information will also be subject to our payment processor’s privacy
policy in addition to ours. PLEASE READ THE PRIVACY POLICY
ON THE WEBSITE OF ANY PAYMENT PROCESSOR THAT YOU ARE DIRECTED TO REGARDING THE
USE,
STORAGE AND PROTECTION OF YOUR CREDIT CARD INFORMATION
BEFORE SUBMITTING ANY CREDIT CARD INFORMATION When you make a charge, we shall
display a completed charge screen. This is your electronic receipt. You should
print or save this electronic receipt for your records. YOU REPRESENT AND
WARRANT THAT YOU HAVE THE LEGAL RIGHT TO USE ANY CREDIT CARDS, DEBIT CARDS OR
OTHER PAYMENT MEANS USED TO INITIATE ANY TRANSACTION.
We may also share your personal
information in the following circumstances
When we are required to provide information in
response to a subpoena, court order, or other applicable law or legal process.
When we have a good faith belief that the
disclosure is necessary to prevent or respond to fraud, defend our apps or
websites against attacks, or protect the property and safety of F2F, our
customers and users, or the public.
If we merge with or are acquired by another
company, sell a F2F website, app, or business unit, or if all or a substantial
portion of our assets are acquired by another company. In those cases, your
information will likely be one of the assets that is transferred.
There are several places within the
Site and our Apps that allow you to post comments or submit Your Content for
others to see. We will display your Personal Information
in your account and elsewhere on our Services according to your subscription
plan.
Any information you choose to provide should reflect how
much you want others to know about you. Please consider
carefully what information you disclose in your profile page and your desired
level of anonymity. You can review and revise your profile information at any
time. To remove Your Content, you have shared on the Site or our Apps, you may
use the same features (available on the Site/Apps) to do so. In case you have
any query regarding removal and or deletion of such contact you can write to us
at privacy@fibre2fashion.com.
We display personal testimonials of customers on our Site in
addition to other endorsements. With your consent, we may post your testimonial
along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can
contact us at   customercare@fibre2fashion.com
Storage and Transfer of Personal Information
Your personal information and files
are stored on F2F's servers and the servers of companies we hire to provide
services to us. Your personal information may be transferred across national
borders because we have servers located in
India and Singapore and the companies we hire to help
us run our business may be located in different countries around the world.
The information that we collect from
you may be transferred to, and stored in, a country outside the European
Economic Area (EEA). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the
EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. The laws in some countries may
not provide as much legal protection for your information as in the EEA. By
submitting your personal information, you agree to this transfer, storing or
processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your
data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.
Unfortunately, the transmission of
information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our
best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of
your information transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk.
Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and
security features to try to prevent unauthorized access.
Security of your information
We understand that the security of your personal information
is important. We provide reasonable administrative, technical, and physical
security controls to protect your personal information. Among other initiatives
that we take to maintain security of your data, we also utilize encryption of
personal data and strict access controls. At the same time, it is important for
you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your
computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. However,
despite our efforts, no security controls are 100% effective and F2F cannot
ensure or warrant the security of your personal information.
Advertising and links to other sites
We display interest-based
advertising on both our sites and unaffiliated sites  using
information you make available to us when you interact with our sites, apps or
services. Interest-based ads, also sometimes referred to as personalized or
targeted ads, are displayed to you based on information from activities including but not limited to purchasing of fibre2fashion magazine
on our site, your interaction with our Services and visiting sites that contain
F2F content or ads.
We use cookies, web beacons and
other technologies (collectively, “cookies and similar technologies”). Cookies
enable us to learn about what ads you see, what ads you click, and other
actions you take on our sites and other sites. This allows us to provide you
with more useful and relevant ads. For example, by knowing what ads you are
shown we can be careful not to show you the same ones repeatedly. For more
information about the use of cookies and similar technologies for
interest-based advertising, please refer to our cookie policy here .
Some of the functionality on our
Services may be provided by third parties that are not affiliated with F2F.
These entities may collect or receive certain information about your use of our
Services and your activities over time and across different websites, including
through the use of cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for,
third-party cookies, web beacons, or other tracking technologies. F2F is not
responsible for the privacy practices of these entities. In addition, our
Services may contain links to other websites not operated or controlled by us.
Such websites are not under our control and we are not responsible for their
privacy policies or practices. If you provide any personal information through
any such third-party website, we recommend that you familiarize yourself with
the privacy policies and practices of that third party.
You
may choose to enable or log in to our Services via various online services like
Google, including social networking services like Facebook, LinkedIn etcetera.
Our services also may enable you to access social networking services such as
Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, or Google (collectively, “Social Network”)
directly or indirectly through our Services.
When you link a Social Network account to
our Apps or log into our Services using your Social Network account, we may
collect relevant information necessary to enable our Services to access that
Social Network and your data contained within that Social Network. We may share
your information with the operator of that Social Network to facilitate or
enhance delivery of that Social Network or other services to you. A Social
Network may provide us with access to certain information that you have
provided to them, and we will use, store, and disclose such information in
accordance with this Privacy Policy. Additionally, a Social Network may collect
personal information and information about your use of our Site or Services
automatically. The manner in which a Social Network collects, uses, stores, and
discloses your information is governed by the policies of such third parties
and F2F shall have no liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or
other actions of any Social Network that may be enabled within its Services.
What rights you have?
Right to be informed:
You are entitled to know whether we hold your personal information and
the purpose your personal data is processed for.
Right of access:
You are entitled to know the categories of your personal data being
processed, the purposes of such processing, and the details of third parties to
whom the data may have been disclosed. For
more details please refer to the list of third parties here.
Right to rectification:
You are entitled to correct / update your personal information available
with us.
Right to erasure:
You are entitled to get your data
erased from our databases. Please note that we might need to retain certain
information about you for reasons including but not limited to legal, internal
business and fraud prevention. We will retain your personal information for as
long as necessary to provide you with the services you are eligible to use and
as needed to comply with our legal obligations and enforce our agreements.
Right to data portability:
You are entitled to obtain and reuse your personal data. You can either
obtain the data from us or, in turn, provide it to a third party (if you so
wish), or ask us to transfer your personal data directly to a third party.
Right to object / restrict processing or both:
You have a right to object / restrict the processing of your data in
some circumstances, including where the data is inaccurate (for the period
during which we are verifying the data), the data is no longer required in
light of the purpose of processing, or in connection with direct marketing (you
can prevent / discontinue marketing communications to you by checking certain
boxes on the forms we use to collect your personal data), or by utilizing
opt-out mechanisms in the emails we send you.
In the above cases, we will retain minimum personal data to note that
you opted out from being contacted again. For
raising requests pertaining to the above-mentioned rights, please write to us at privacy@fibre2fashion.com . Please note some of
the rights mentioned herein may not be available as we are designing the
technical capabilities to comply with such requests; having said the above F2F
will do its best to resolve your request to the best of its ability.
Privacy of Children
We recognize the
importance of children's safety and privacy. We do not request, or knowingly
collect, any personally identifiable information from children under the age of
18. F2F is very sensitive to privacy issues regarding children. By visiting
this Site or providing your personal information to one of our call-centre
operators or live chat representatives or starting your free trial or signing
up or logging in you are claiming yourself to be 18 years of age or above.
If you believe that
any child under the age of 18 has posted any personal information anywhere on
our website, please contact us immediately at
privacy@fibre2fashion.com and provide as much information as you can to help us
locate and delete the personal information.
If a parent or
guardian becomes aware that his or her child or any other child under the age
of 18 has provided us with personal information, he or she should write to us at privacy@fibre2fashion.com
California Do Not Track
F2F does not have a
mechanism in place for responding to browser “do not track” signals or other similar mechanisms used to
limit collection of information for use in Online Behavioural Advertising.
There currently is no consensus among industry participants as to what "Do
Not Track" means in this context. Therefore, like many websites and online
services, the Services do not alter their practices when they receive a
"Do Not Track" signal from a visitor's browser. To find out more
about "Do Not Track," please visit http://www.allaboutdnt.com.
Questions/Changes to policy
F2F welcomes your
comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you believe that we have not adhered
to this Policy or If you have questions or concerns with respect to our Privacy
Policy, please write to us at
privacy@fibre2fashion.com
×Third Party Sites
A third party to us and you in the context of our privacy notice includes but is not limited to our business partners, suppliers, sub-contractors, advertisers & advertising networks, analytics & search engine providers, sales and marketing partners, payment providers (hereinafter collectively referred to as “third parties”). The following third parties may use tools and technologies including but not limited to cookies, web beacons, pixels, local storage, sessions storage etcetera.
These companies may collect information about other apps on your various devices, the websites you visit, location information, and other information. In addition, we may share information with partners for Service improvements, research and analysis, to help us provide you more meaningful experiences and content and to help us communicate with you about any offers from us.
For more information, please review their privacy policies.
Subscribe today and get the latest information on Textiles, Fashion, Apparel.
Fibre2Fashion Monthly Updates
Upcoming Trade fairs & Events Monthly
Daily eNews Insights
Technical Textiles eNews Weekly
Please refer our Privacy Policy before submitting your information
